(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 21=
(Plagiarism is shameless!)
(Don't go around accusing people)
(You plagiarized!?)
(of "borrowing ideas".)
(Clout-chasing!)
(This isn't a tribute.)
(Absurd! Boycott!)
(This is straight-up plagiarism.)
(I've followed this book for two years.)
(He's not that kind of person.)
(- I compared them.
- Mixing in other people's ideas)
(- Those are public elements.
- is not a free pass.)
(- This is worse than I thought.
- It's plagiarism.)
(It's an alternate account.)
(Slapping a new skin on it
is even worse than copying it outright.)
(If similar content means plagiarism,)
(then no web novel should ever
be written anymore.)
(Boycott Shattered Six States!
Boycott He Han!)
(I've supported you for years,
and you plagiarized?)
(Shanghai Xintuo Fasteners Wholesale)
(Thanks.)
Did you see those comments
accusing you of borrowing ideas?
Aren't you going to clear this up?
Lin Zhanqiao, can you stay out of this?
Dai Shan's already
hounding me with questions.
Don't add fuel to the fire.
How am I adding fuel to the fire?
Are you aware
that once public opinion takes off,
it can go either way?
If Mr. Fan sits back and watches,
that's already being nice to you.
But if he starts fanning the flames
and this blows up,
it might even benefit the platform
with more traffic and attention.
But for you,
it'll definitely hurt you.
You know we can clarify this.
When you wrote Shattered Six States,
you were still with Chenxing.
I was your editor.
So I have a responsibility
to step in and speak for you.
You don't.
And you're not my editor anymore.
What happens with this book
is between Dai Shan and me.
You have no right to interfere.
(Amy: So disappointed.
Followed this novel for so long.)
(Source Code replies to Amy:
Exactly. Thought he was a great author.)
Someone suddenly pulls out
Parting Yan Dan at Yishui,
and tell mes it was written by
Phantom Knight five years ago.
Can't I also say he
or anyone wrote it after reading
Shattered Six States?
I'm here to discuss this,
right?
You can't just say things like that.
The editor has all the emails.
There are timestamps on everything.
Of course.
It hasn't reached the level
of an IP dispute.
But there is public backlash now.
It's only right
that we prepare something.
An author's reputation matters, right?
Especially He Han's reputation.
That's our top priority to protect.
How do you want to do?
You've noticed something off,
haven't you?
That's exactly why
I wanted to talk to you.
He's on hiatus now, right?
Let's just leave
what happened before this.
But if there's any more backlash,
do not respond.
Also, that part
about "turning back
and seeing him again",
needs to be revised.
It has to be changed.
I'm worried it'll get blown out again.
Talk to him about it.
Honestly, I'm curious.
Just personally.
I didn't mean anything.
How did He Han
get access to Phantom Knight's
unpublished manuscript?
That's impossible.
He couldn't have seen it.
He can be unreliable sometimes,
but not to the point
of risking everything over this.
This is the first time
I've seen you defend someone like this.
He Han has a lot of fans.
But he probably didn't expect
Phantom Knight's fans to be
several times more.
The author has disappeared for years,
(Plagiarism is unforgivable)
and the fans disappeared, too.
(For real? Did you read it?)
Now that something has happened,
everyone suddenly realizes
how many people support that author.
I didn't expect
the current top spot
to be Phantom Knight.
An author who vanished for years
and an unfinished manuscript
still carry this much weight.
Mr. Fan really knows what he's doing.
I even think
this whole mess
was orchestrated by him.
So He Han
is out of the sequel, right?
I think this is
actually a great move for you.
Lin Zhanqiao doesn't want me
to do the sequel.
What about you?
Of course I want to write it.
What if you write under a new pen name?
Will that be a problem?
Chenxing and I...
I'm not signing you.
Who do you trust most?
I'll sign with them.
I'll handle Mr. Fan's side.
Get back to me as soon as possible.
(Mengtong Internet Cafe)
Orange juice.
Scan to pay.
(I've supported you for years,
and you plagiarized?)
(Replies to Let's Dance: What proof
do you have that He Han plagiarized?)
(Don't sway public opinion!
He didn't plagiarize!)
Why aren't the lights on?
Ms. Lin,
Mr. He Han is getting attacked.
I'm trying to defend him.
But Phantom Knight's fans are too many.
I can't keep up with them.
How can you fight
that many people alone?
I know I can't win,
but I just can't stay quiet.
How can they say things like that
about Mr. He Han?
Plagiarism and clout-chasing?
It's making me pissed off!
Alright.
Whoever insults Mr. He Han,
I'll fire back at all of them.
It's late. You haven't eaten, right?
Let's go.
I can't eat.
Alright. Calm down. Come on.
Look at this profile picture.
You can tell
they're not a decent person!
Yeah, I know.
They're just asking to be roasted.
He'll handle it himself.
One statement from him
is more effective
than you typing all night.
But he hasn't said anything.
Something happened to him recently.
And with this mess now,
he probably doesn't have the mood
to respond.
Has he contacted you?
I've tried reaching out to him,
but he screens my calls and texts.
That just proves
he's in a really bad state right now.
I'm honestly scared
he might stop writing because of this.
There are only a few days left
of his one-week break.
Fans arguing with each other is normal.
It'll calm down soon.
It's not that simple.
Phantom Knight's fans
have started boycotting He Han
and Shattered Six States.
The streaming platform bought
the TV adaptation
of Shattered Six States,
and now those fans
are boycotting
the drama, too.
Why do they get to do that?
Fuel up on orange juice,
and let's keep going.
The platform's legal team called.
They said the authorization details
for Shattered Six States
might need to be renegotiated.
Don't sell it to them.
It's not like they're the only buyer.
I don't think it's a big deal.
They probably just want to wait
until the novel is nearly finished
and the controversy dies down
before paying the rest.
Honestly,
their offer is still pretty high.
As long as they don't cut the price,
we can make
some small concessions.
I'll leave it to you.
Don't read the comments.
It'll mess with your mood.
It's not that serious.
It's not like this is my first day
writing web novels. I've heard worse.
At most, they'll call me a plagiarist,
say I've run out of ideas.
I've done nothing wrong.
Can you not reply to the comments?
I won't.
Don't worry.
You should head back early.
You've got two days
before your update resumes.
I know.
I'll get going then.
Let's talk in my room.
Are you okay?
Why did you come all the way here?
Because you refused to see me.
I had no choice but to come here.
I was working on a case.
It's a very tricky one.
I didn't have a single moment free
until tonight.
See?
I came straight to you
right after I finished.
Even if you hadn't come
to Yichun tonight,
I would've gone to Shanghai
to find you tomorrow.
(New Recording)
You know
I came to see you about
the company under my name, right?
You're the one in control of it.
Now the company's in trouble.
There are things
I need to ask you.
Turn off the recording.
Did Zhang Yousen tell you to do this?
Is he here, too?
Your young boyfriend
thinks too simply.
Fine.
If you want to record, go ahead.
I know what you want to ask.
I'll keep it simple.
The six million plus in unpaid taxes
under your company's name
will be covered by me.
You don't need to worry.
As for this company,
you can keep it or shut it down.
That's up to you.
Tell Zhang Yousen
he doesn't need to rack his brain,
trying to come up with
a perfect solution for you.
From the first day I met you,
I decided that nothing
would ever hurt you
or let you feel upset.
How do I know you're telling the truth?
When you get to Shanghai tomorrow,
your finance team will tell you
all the taxes have been paid.
This isn't
a small amount of money.
Whether it's a lot or a little,
that's my problem.
I'll handle it.
You shouldn't have to worry
about this anymore.
Six million plus
with late fees,
it's around seven million.
Can you come up with that much
at once?
Are you worried about me?
I just don't want you to rob Peter
to pay Paul.
No.
Aside from this company
I'm working with you,
I don't have anything else anymore.
There is something
I need to tell you.
I've told my wife
everything.
She's going to help me cover this money.
What do you mean?
She knows the company is under my name?
Yes.
I told her
I set it up
for work and financial dealings.
Does she believe you?
Whether she believes it or not
doesn't matter.
What matters is that I've promised her
that from now on,
we'll draw a clear line.
There'll be
no more contact.
You and the company?
The company
and you.
You say no more contact.
Will I still be able to see you?
You deserve a better man
and life.
(How did the talk go?)
(Zhang Yousen: How did the talk go?)
♪If the sky and the sea traded places♪
♪If a fish fell in love with a bird♪
♪If we hadn't wavered♪
You shouldn't have come here.
♪We wouldn't have lost each other
in the crowd♪
I really shouldn't have come.
♪We met in the thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪Let love surge like raging waves♪
♪Crashing over us, never fading♪
♪Even if we're drenched in the rain♪
♪Even if time buries us away♪
♪At least we still have♪
♪This one eternal photo♪
♪Let's not lose each other again♪
♪People only realize what matters
after losing it♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll grow old together♪
♪But the sky can never trade places
with the sea♪
♪And a fish will never fall in love
with a bird♪
(Rukawa Kaeda: Plagiarist! Get lost!
Refund!)
(Zhanzhu replies to Rukawa Kaeda:
He did not plagiarize!)
(He took the photo of you, didn't he?)
(The big fan is losing it
before the author even says a word.)
What's wrong?
Didn't I tell you
not to argue with them?
You can't win against them.
Alright. That's enough.
Let me see.
They're piling on you online.
These are edited, right?
I don't know how they got them.
That is my face,
but I've never worn those clothes.
They...
They're saying
I'm that kind of person.
They're asking how much
Mr. He Han paid me.
I'll report this to the police
and file a complaint with the platform.
Can you not reply to the comments?
(Replies to "Photoshopped or a boob job?
Might as well invest in a brain".)
(People can really be this confident.
Is it ignorance?)
(Living up to your username!)
(Replies to Rukawa Kaeda:
Did he tell you that in bed?)
(Come to my bed, I'll tell you myself!)
(Melon Thief Critter:
What gives you the right)
(to prove He Han innocent
by typing a few words?)
(What's your relationship with him?
He hasn't even said anything.)
(Replies to Melon Thief Critter:
Here's my advice: Get offline for now.)
(What you need to do is jump into
a pot with cabbage and vermicelli.)
(He Han replies to Rukawa Kaeda:
Come to my bed, I'll tell you myself!)
(Zhangzhu replies:
You don't read any of his work.)
(He Han replies to Melon Thief Critter:
Here's my advice: Get offline for now)
(What you need to do is jump into
a pot with cabbage and vermicelli.)
Ms. Lin.
Mr. He Han replied.
Look at this.
He's done for.
What are you guys doing?
Say no more.
I know I shouldn't have replied to
those trolls.
But I really couldn't hold it in.
They can say
whatever they want about me.
But smearing and attacking
a young girl like that
is disgusting.
Did you see those photos?
I can't just watch my readers
take the hits for me
while I hide behind them and
sit on my hands.
Don't worry. I won't let things
get out of hand.
Listen to me.
No more posting.
I want to help Mr. He Han.
We all do.
But not in this way.
(Recipient: Ma,
Subject: Statement on Phantom Knight)
Lawyer Bei has left.
I've broken up with him.
We were both wrong.
He'll take responsibility
for the company's debt.
I didn't realize
you loved him that much!
So we should break up as well.
But I don't want to break up with you.
You and I were
never really in a relationship.
That's because
Lawyer Bei was around before.
Not that he's gone.
It's a good thing for me.
But I won't love anyone again.
That's not necessarily true.
I can prove it to you.
You've seen it?
Happy?
Why would I be happy?
I don't want any of you to get hurt.
I care about how Dingqi does,
and I care just as much about
whether you win or lose.
The streaming platform wants to
renegotiate the contract.
They want a price cut, right?
How much?
Half.
That's tricky.
You already secured
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui.
Can't you contact Phantom Knight?
We have only talked to Ma.
Phantom Knight's agent.
This person is overseas now.
So you're saying
only Ma
can reach Phantom Knight?
Yes.
Don't expect the agent
to reveal anything.
And this time,
don't expect him
to bring Phantom Knight out either.
(Luo Jingjing)
The sequel contract
for Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui
has been signed.
The news should be out soon.
Who did you get to write it?
A newbie.
Fan, what exactly
are you up to?
By the way,
I don't want
Lin Zhanqiao's company anymore.
(New author Sansan continues
the legend of Phantom Knight!)
Who's Sansan?
Zhao Lanxin found this person.
No idea.
The update drops tonight.
We'll see what Sansan has got.
I don't remember any of the newcomers
she poached from us
called Sansan.
I think Sansan's a girl.
Hard to say.
This is the first time
we're working with an author like this.
It shows
we trust each other enough.
Did you read what I sent?
Yeah.
The editor read it, too.
You're a genius.
Tonight, everyone will see
a new author, Sansan,
come into the spotlight.
I'm starting to understand
how Phantom Knight felt.
Famous name
and no face.
It's kind of thrilling.
(Ma: Copyright regarding Phantom Knight
and Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui)
(Phantom Knight
Sir, would you like gold-filled
engraving and an incense burner?
No.
Alright.
Let's go.
(Grave of Late Father, He Wei)
(Guizhou Moutai)
Why did you pick
such a nice spot for him?
No need to do all that.
He wouldn't care.
As long as there's alcohol, he's fine.
You think he doesn't care,
but I think he cares a lot.
Now he can drink as much as he wants.
Give him a toast.
You two are the worst father and son
I've ever seen.
At least now, you're both free.
He Wei.
He Han.
Both are free.
To be honest, I kind of miss him.
It's not what you think.
It's just that back then,
he was my excuse for being a mess.
Now that he's gone,
that excuse is gone, too.
Dad.
This is my last drink.
From today on,
I'm quitting.
How are you going to do
with those trolls?
I leave it to Dai Shan.
She doesn't know the truth
about Phantom Knight.
No one does.
I emailed Ma yesterday.
I wanted to see
if he would come out and say something.
He replied.
He said
he didn't think things through
when he sold the rights.
So he's willing
to step in
as the current rights holder
and the former editor to mediate.
That won't help.
It's just a hollow official statement.
I know.
But that's our only option now.
Unless...
we reveal
Phantom Knight's identity.
Don't be ridiculous.
This isn't life or death.
It's just a novel.
Phantom Knight appeals to the public
because of his mysterious identity.
If you reveal his identity,
what's left?
If this keeps blowing up online,
I'm worried it'll hurt
your reputation in the industry.
I'll handle it myself.
This has nothing to do with you
or Phantom Knight.
Where were you last night?
I went on a business trip.
Where to?
Yichun.
Which hotel did you stay at?
Xinggui Hotel.
Why did you do your hair?
And you came back wearing high heels.
Work event.
What about all these?
Did you buy this much makeup
also for a work event?
No.
You bought these for yourself?
What are you trying to do?
Nothing.
I just want to look better.
Your natural look is already the best.
You don't need makeup to cover anything.
You can throw the rest away.
These two are expensive.
I'll keep them.
Where did you get the nerve
to go against me?
Which man is it?
There isn't one.
I bought them with my own money.
It would be a waste to throw them away.
You're spending too much
on makeup.
If you can earn your own living,
there's no need
to buy these things to please a man.
Explain yourself.
What exactly are you thinking?
I'm tired.
Actually, I've been exhausted lately.
I don't have the energy
to explain myself.
Think whatever you want.
What has gotten into you?
You weren't like this before.
I'll throw these two away.
Happy now?
If you are, can you leave?
I want to sleep.
You all have probably heard
Dingqi has backed out
of investing in Chenxing.
Because of He Han's online backlash?
The plan was for He Han
to return to Chenxing
and boost our valuation.
Look what has happened now.
He can barely save himself.
From what I know, Dingqi
Reading platform might switch over
to Zhao Lanxin's company.
I also heard
the author Zhao Lanxin signed
to continue
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui
is good.
It's hard to believe
they would hand such
a big project to a newcomer.
Well, has Gu Yan
turned in his manuscript?
Yeah. It's pretty decent.
He's been submitting on time lately.
We can't lose
Gu Yan.
On that basis,
we should bring in
one or two authors at his level.
In that case, we'll have something
to attract new investment.
What Zhao Lanxin's company is doing,
pushing a bunch of new authors
to climb the ranking is also a strategy.
If we can secure
the game adaptation rights,
it should take some pressure off.
Gu Yan also mentioned
that he wants to start a new project.
We could consider that.
Personally, I'll invest more money.
That should
at least
buy us another six months.
(Baijiu Property)
(Urgent Sale: Van Gogh Apartment)
You're back to regular updates tonight.
Are you ready?
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui
will be updated today too.
Dingqi will definitely throw
their best resources at it.
It's both a new
and a major project for them.
Can you handle this?
Isn't it better
if they take the heat for us?
Otherwise, once I resume updates,
there'll be a bunch of people
who don't even read it,
just here to stir things up
and trash it.
The streaming platform called.
They want to cut the royalties in half.
I'll try to keep it
to no more than a ten percent cut.
Didn't I say I'm not selling it?
If we don't sell,
we have to return the deposit.
Then return it.
How much is it?
Seven million.
That much?
Also, according to the contract,
as long as I'm not at fault,
I don't return the portion I've taken.
Of course.
I don't know how much I still have left,
but it should be enough
to cover it, right?
You used to have a lot of money.
Do you know
how much your hotel costs per day?
6,500.
That's 200,000
a month,
over two million a year.
And that doesn't include
food, alcohol, and laundry.
Plus the car I bought.
Right.
And all the gifts
you gave your girlfriend
and your female friends
for Chinese New Year, holidays,
and birthdays.
Hey,
they're all readers.
As an author, it's only right
to treat your readers well
and keep them around.
Making those young and pretty girls
who love to read
happy is a wonderful thing
to do, isn't it?
I give gifts to male readers, too.
Sure, they're wonderful.
Add it all up,
that's a few million at least.
And that's just what I know.
There's more I don't.
Fine.
I'll figure out the money.
You get the rights back.
I'm not selling them.
Alright.
Let me remind you.
While you're raising money,
don't forget to include my salary.
I don't get paid peanuts.
Let me ask you.
If I can't pay you,
will you leave?
I will.
And per contract,
you'll owe six months' compensation.
Nice.
Let's see who this Sansan really is.
Hopefully,
it's not another Gu Yan.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪